Viewers all over the world, anywhere you are, distance is not a barrier - just believe.
I can see you. I can see the disposition of your heart, says the Lord.
I can see your heart's desire, says the Lord.
I can see the thought of your heart, says the Lord.
Begin to receive, in the name of Jesus!
[Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name]
You, barrier - be removed, in the name of Jesus!
The barrier between your heart and the Spirit of the Father - be caged, in the name of Jesus!
[Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name]
Begin to receive, in the name of Jesus!
Receive, in the Name of Jesus!
I can hear someone saying, "I am sick; pray for me".
Receive your healing, in the name of Jesus!
[Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name]
I can hear you say, "I am poor".
You are restored, in the name of Jesus!
[Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name]
Business challenges - you are delivered, in the name of Jesus!
I speak to your career - be restored!
I speak to your health - be restored!
I speak to your family - be restored!
[Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name]
Be restored!
Be restored, in the name of Jesus Christ!
I want to say to you, "Breakthrough!"
This is the voice of the Holy Spirit and when the Holy Spirit speaks, changes are beginning.
Breakthrough!
In your career - breakthrough!
In your future - breakthrough!
In your family - breakthrough!
I say, "Breakthrough!"
In your marriage - breakthrough!
In your finances - breakthrough!
In your business - breakthrough!
[Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name]
In Jesus Christ’s Name!
Jesus is the same yesterday, today and forever.
When I say, “Breakthrough”, I am not speaking my own words; this is the Word of the Holy Spirit.
Whether you like it or not, you are not going to be the same again!
In the Name of Jesus!
Your business is not going to be the same again!
Your career is not going to be the same again!
Your finances are not going to be the same again!
They are not going to be the same again, in Jesus' name!
[Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name]
Rejoice!
Hallelujah!